The Recovery Time Objective,
恢复时间目标
or RTO, is the maximum duration of a service interruption.
或 RTO  是服务中断的最大持续时间
This is the time that you agree to in your SLA.
这是您在 SLA中同意的时间
Of course, it is possible that you will fail to meet your RTO.
当然 您可能无法满足您的 RTO
In this case, any penalties in your contracts will come into play.
在此情况下 您的合同中的任何惩罚都将生效
RTO is similar to uptime,
RTO 类似于 uptime
but it is measured per incident,
但每宗事件都有
rather than on a monthly basis.
而不是按月计算
Really, your RTO should be small enough so that
你的 RTO 应该足够小
at least one outage would still fit within your uptime SLA.
至少一次中断在您的正常服务等级协议中仍然适用
Otherwise, you can meet your RTO,
否则你可以见见你的 RTO
SLA, but still miss your overall uptime SLA.
SLA  但仍未满足您的总体正常运行时间 SLA
As with uptime, you need to carefully consider what RTO you can support.
与正常运行时间一样 您需要仔细考虑您可以支持的 RTO
All of the critical parts of your platform must be
平台的所有关键部分都必须是
designed for recovery within your RTO timeframe.
用于在 RTO 时间范围内进行恢复
Lots of things must happen to restore service to your platform.
为您的平台恢复服务必须发生许多事情
When thinking about RTO,
当想到 RTO时
don't forget about the human factor type of things such as getting people out of bed,
别忘了人的因素类型比如把人从床上
or searching for the right documentation.
或寻找正确的文档
Your RTO should be the sum of the time it takes to
你的 RTO 应该是
complete all of the components of a recovery from failure.
完成从故障恢复的所有组件
If it takes two hours to restore a database from a backup,
如果从备份中恢复数据库需要两个小时
you cannot have a one hour RTO.
您不能有一个小时 RTO
Be sure you have plans for staff to be on-call,
请确保您有员工来电的计划
and that those staff know how to recover your systems,
那些员工知道如何恢复你的系统
or at least get in touch with other subject matter experts as needed.
或者至少可以根据需要与其他主题专家联系